

CARLOS HINOJOSA PINTO

https://www.carlosh.es

ABOUT ME

I am a Computer Engineering graduate from the Polytechnic University of Valencia, in Spain with more than 3 years of experience in the field. I love to learn new things and acquire new skills every day, in my free time I like to read, going to the gym and run in the mountain.

TECH SKILLS

Computer Languages:

- JavaScript/Typescript
- PHP
- Python

- Java
- HTML/CSS
- C/C++

Tecnologies:

- React
- Node JS
- Docker
- Laravel
- Unit testing
- NextJS
- Wordpress
- Git
- Bootstrap
- MySQL

SOFT SKILLS

- Agile methodologies
- Teamwork and collaboration
- Goal-oriented mindset

Languages:

- Spanish(Native)
- English (B2)

CONTACT

Telephone: (+34)664 099 349 carloshin98@gmail.com https://www.carlosh.es



EXPERIENCE

IOBUILDERS

Frontend developer

September 2021 - Now

Frontend developer using **React** with **TypeScript** and testing with **Jest**. Creating a NFT Marketplace for DC COMIC in the Palm Blockchain. Working with a team in different time zones and with meetings in English.

NTT DATA

Frontend developer

November 2020 - September 2021

Frontend developer, using **Angular** with **Typescript** for develop a modern web application for a bank.

MULTISCAN TECHNOLOGIES (INTERSHIP)

Software developer

January 2020 - May 2020

Software developer, I used C++ and Python for programming scanners that detects fruit and vegetables defects.

ACTIVALINK (INTERSHIP)

Fullstack developer

March 2019- September 2019

Fullstack developer using for backend MySQL database and React and jQuery for the frontend

EDUCATION

UPV http://www.upv.es

Computer Engineering Degree

September 2016 - June 2020

PROYECTS

SELL CARS https://sell-car-carlosh.vercel.app/cars

Web to publish cars using **NextJS** with **Typescript** and **Chakra UI** for styles.

TFG https://www.tfg.carlosh.es/app/

Final proyect for the Computer Science Degree. This web allow you to order food from a restaurant. Done with **PHP** and **React**.

WEB MIGUEL PINTO https://miguel-pinto.vercel.app/

Web made in **NextJS** and **Typescript** for the promotion of the painter Miguel Pinto.

WEB BOOKS https://www.libros.carlosh.es

Web application to store book collections developed with Laravel.